

Email

iloudaros@upnet.gr

Phone Number

+30 6940504030

Languages

Greek

English

Skills

Programming Languages

C, C++, Java, Swift, Python, MatLab, Javascript, HTML, CSS

Experienced with

Office Suite, iWork Suite, GSuite, Trello, Monday

Github, Xcode, Atom

Adobe Creative Cloud, Final Cut Pro, Motion, Compressor, Vectornator, Pixelmator Pro, Figma

Others

Classical Piano, Break Dance, Jazz, Cheers, Acro



iloudaros



Ioannis Loudaros



Ioannis Loudaros | Ιωάννης Λουδάρος

A passionate student of Computer Engineering and Informatics. With extended experience in event management and preeminent academic presence. Having already carried out ambitious endeavours in the fields of Art, Volunteering and Engineering, he is no stranger to challenges. Used to responsibilities, as the PR Person of the IEEE Student Branch of Patras. He is ultimately armed with technical knowledge, as well as, the art of communication and cooperation.

Featured in



The Uni.Times: IEEE Student Branch - University of Patras with Ioannis Loudaros

A small interview about the IEEE SB of the University of Patras. I was the PR Person at the time.

Education

Παρακαλώ ελάτε πίσω αργότερα, πραγματοποιούνται δοκιμές αυτοματοποίησης!

University of Patras, Computer Engineering and Informatics Department Integrated Masters in Computer Engineering and Informatics, 5th year (final).

2nd High School of Ilion

Graduated with Commendation.

Volunteering

Acting Team

2nd High School of Ilion Sept 2013 - May 2016 · 3 yrs

Journalism Team

2nd High School of Ilion Sept 2013 - May 2015 · 2 yrs

Fundraising, Social, Design

IEEE SB UPatras May 2019 - Dec 2019 · 8 mos

Courses

Arduino essentials

Seminar at the Mediterranean College

MATLAB Onramp

Associated with University of Patras

Experience

Reception at "Wave Sports" in Thera

Wave Sports · Aug 2016

Reception and preparation of the customers for the maritime activities.

Freelance Video Editor

Ongoing

Examples such as: "Φροντιστήρια Πουκαμισάς" (Video for the opening of the company's new building) and Beauty Aifel (Instagram promotion Video).

Secretary / PR Supervisor

IEEE SB UPatras

Dec 2019 - Jun 2021 · 1 yr 7 mos

With a really active presence in the organisation and coordination of many scientific and social events like: IEEE Day, IEEE Xtreme, Spooktacular Uparty, Google HashCode Hub etc.

Mentor

IEEE SB UPatras Jun 2021 - Present

Insider (Tour Guide)

Athens Insiders · Part-time Aug 2021 - Sep 2022

Designed and executed tours with special content.

Model and Actor

Attitude Models · Part-time Jan 2022 - Present

Did extra roles for films and ads for brands such as "What'sUp", "Payze", "Nescafe" etc.

Projects

You can have access to selected projects listed here and more, by clicking the GitHub link on the previous page.

nomnomr.

Associated with University of Patras

A tool for the nights when you wanna kill your friends. Group orders have never been easier and more fun.

CoVID69

Associated with University of Patras

A University Project on how to blow Covid-19 away. Community based infection reporting.

Order

Associated with University of Patras

Set of logistic tools that track objects of interest inside of a building using RFID technology, a mobile app, and QR Codes.

Hot Sauce

Associated with University of Patras

A simple Lexical and Syntactical Analyser for a C-like language made with Flex and Bison.

Paralllelli

Associated with University of Patras

University Project on the subject of Parallel Computing. It explores parallelization techniques using OpenMP, MPI, or a combination of both.

Tourism Analysis using the Eurostat Python package

Associated with University of Patras

Using data from Eurostat, we get to some conclusions related to tourism in Greece and Spain

Art Projects

Sound Art Seminar for Music Professors by Panagiotis Vasilellis

The goal of this seminar was to prove that students with no musical studies -but with aesthetics and passion- can create impressive audio experiences. I was the curator of the ambient sounds that tied the individual sounds of the students.

Video for March 25th

Creation of a video that contained historical and cultural information around the anniversary. It was projected at a relevant event.

"ΤΙΣΙΣ, ΜΙΑ ΟΝΤΟΤΗΤΑ ΤΗΣ ΘΑΛΑΣΣΑΣ" by Panagiotis Vasilellis

Performance based on sound art and narration. It was part of a sea themed Art Exhibition . It was presented in a gallery in Plaka, Athens. I was the narrator.

Biographical Video for Kiki Dimoula

Biographical video for the biggest greek poetess alive. It contained an exclusive recording of the poem "Dust" by Aristea Papalexandrou.